Register of the Robert H. Malott letters received
Hoover Institution Archives
- Letters received, 1971-2013
  - Webster, William, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box-folder 7: 42)
  - Weidenbaum, Murray, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 7: 43)
  - Weinberger, Caspar, 1983, 1987 (Box-folder 7: 44)
  - Welch, Larry, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 45)
  - Wheeler, W. H., 1971 (Box-folder 7: 46)
  - White, Robert, 1991 (Box-folder 7: 47)
  - Whitehead, John, 1988 (Box-folder 7: 48)
  - Whitten, Jamie, 1987 (Box-folder 7: 49)
  - Whittlesey, Faith, 1984 (Box-folder 7: 50)
  - Williamson, Richard, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 7: 51)
  - Wilson, Charles, 1987, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 52)
  - Wilson, Michael, 1993 (Box-folder 7: 53)
  - Wilson, Pete, 1988, 1990, 1994 (Box-folder 7: 54)
  - Wolf, Dale, 1989 (Box-folder 7: 55)
  - Wörner, Manfred, 1990-1991, 1994 (Box-folder 7: 56)
  - Wright, Joseph, 1988 (Box-folder 7: 57)
  - Wright, Oliver, 1986 (Box-folder 7: 58)
  - Wriston, Walter, 1985 (Box-folder 7: 59)
  - Xu, Han, 1986, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 60)
  - Yeutter, Clayton, 1985-1991, 1996 (Box-folder 7: 61)
  - Yew, Lee, 1982 (Box-folder 7: 62)
  - Yiren, Rong, 1984 (Box-folder 7: 63)
  - Youde, Pamela, 1986 (Box-folder 7: 64)
  - Younger, George, 1986 (Box-folder 7: 65)
  - Zhu, Rongji, 1989, 1991 (Box-folder 7: 66)
  - Zhu, Quizhen, 1990 (Box-folder 7: 67)
  - Zumwalt, Elmo, 1983, 1991 (Box-folder 7: 68)
  - Zwack, Peter, 1990 (Box-folder 8: 437: 69)
  - Unidentified, 1987 (Box-folder 7: 70)
- Ephemera, 1984
  - Menu from the Honorable Quan Shu-ren Executive Mansion, 1984 (Box-folder 7: 71)